A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files, 1967-1979; 11; 88 Cubic Feet 204 document cases
  - Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files - Administration File, 11.A
    - Papers (Box 117, Folder 955)
      Eisner, Elliot W., n.d. Foshay, Arthur, 1973-1974 Grove, Richard, 1968-1971
    - Papers (Box 118, Folder 956)
      Hausman, Jerome J., 1970-1972 Hopson, J., 1973 Josman, M., 1972 Morrison, Jack W., 1975
    - Papers - Remer, Jane, 1973-1978 (Box 118, Folder 957)
    - Papers - Remer, Jane, 1973-1978 (Box 118, Folder 958)
    - Papers (Box 118, Folder 959)
      Stake, Robert, 1973 Summer, L. D., 1971 Topping, L. Martin, n.d.
    - Personnel - Applications (A-K) (Box 118, Folder 960)
    - Personnel - Applications (A-K) (Box 118, Folder 961)
    - Personnel - Applications (L-Z) (Box 119, Folder 962)
    - Personnel - Applications (L-Z) (Box 119, Folder 963)
    - Personnel - References (Box 119, Folder 964)
    - Publications - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 965)
    - Publications - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 966)
    - Publications - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 120, Folder 967)
    - Publications - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 120, Folder 968)
    - Publications - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 120, Folder 969)
    - Publications - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 120, Folder 970)
    - Publications - Correspondence - Kathryn Bloom, 1968-1973 (Box 120, Folder 971)
    - Publications - Correspondence - Kathryn Bloom, 1968-1973 (Box 120, Folder 972)
    - Publications - JDR 3rd Fund - "IMPACT and Basic Skills" (Box 121, Folder 973)
    - Publications - JDR 3rd Fund - General Brochure, 1969 (Box 121, Folder 974)
    - Publications - JDR 3rd Fund - "Arts in Education", 1971 (Box 121, Folder 975)
    - Publications, 1969; 1973 (Box 121, Folder 976)
      John D. Rockefeller, 3rd - "The Arts in Education," 1969 John D. Rockefeller, 3rd - "The Second American Revolution," 1973
    - Publications - Kathryn Bloom - "All the Arts for All the Children", 1973 (Box 121, Folder 977)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests, 1974-1979 (Box 121, Folder 978)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests, 1974-1979 (Box 121, Folder 979)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Alabama-California) (Box 121, Folder 980)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Chidlren" - Requests (Colorado-District of Columbia) (Box 122, Folder 981)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Florida-Illinois) (Box 122, Folder 982)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Indiana-Maryland) (Box 122, Folder 983)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Massachusetts-Michigan) (Box 122, Folder 984)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Minnesota-New Hampshire) (Box 122, Folder 985)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (New Jersey) (Box 122, Folder 986)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (New Mexico-New York) (Box 123, Folder 987)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (North Carolina-Ohio) (Box 123, Folder 988)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Oklahoma-Pennsylvania) (Box 123, Folder 989)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Rhode Island-Vermont) (Box 123, Folder 990)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests (Virginia-Wisconsin) (Box 123, Folder 991)
    - Publications - "All the Arts for All the Children" - Requests, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 992)
      Canada, other Foreign Requests, and general report on distribution.
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Final Draft, 1975 (Box 124, Folder 993)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Intermediate Draft, Chapters 2, 4, and 6 (Box 124, Folder 994)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Draft (Box 124, Folder 995)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Draft (Box 124, Folder 996)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Draft (Box 124, Folder 997)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Draft (Box 124, Folder 998)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Draft (Box 124, Folder 999)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 124, Folder 1000)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 124, Folder 1001)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 124, Folder 1002)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Promotion, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1003)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Promotional Luncheon, June 3, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 1004)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Invoices, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 1005)
    - Publications - Robert Stake, ed. - "Evaluating the Arts in Education: A Responsive Approach" - Royalty Statements, 1975-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1006)
    - Publications - Wenner, Gene C. - "Dance in the Schools" - Copy of Publication and Final Draft, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 1007)
    - Publications - Wenner, Gene C. - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 125, Folder 1008)
    - Speeches, 1967-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1009)
    - Subscriptions, 1969 (Box 125, Folder 1010)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1011)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1012)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1013)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1014)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1015)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1016)
    - Subscriptions - Youth Task Force, 1970-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1017)
    - Subscriptions - Miscellany, 1969-1974 (Box 127, Folder 1018)
    - Subscriptions - Clippings (Box 127, Folder 1019)
  - Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files - Project Files, 11.B
    This subseries is an alphabetical file consisting of correspondence, memoranda, grant files, brochures, publications, records of meetings, site visits and conferences, curriculum material, and financial data related to the projects undertaken or supported by the Arts in Education Program.
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Memoranda - Gene C. Wenner, 1970-1976 (Box 127, Folder 1020)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 127, Folder 1021)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Meetings (Box 127, Folder 1022)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1023)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Declaration of Interdependence, 1976 (Box 128, Folder 1024)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 128, Folder 1025)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Memoranda, 1975-1979 (Box 128, Folder 1026)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Proposal to National Endowment for the Humanities, 1975-1976 (Box 128, Folder 1027)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Miscellany, 1975-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1028)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Correspondence (Box 128, Folder 1029)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Materials (Box 129, Folder 1030)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Mailing List (Box 129, Folder 1031)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Information Enclosures (Box 129, Folder 1032)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Information Enclosures (Box 129, Folder 1033)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Information Enclosures (Box 129, Folder 1034)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Information Enclosures (Box 130, Folder 1035)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Conference, May 19-20, 1975 - Information Enclosures (Box 130, Folder 1036)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Comprehensive Arts Planning Booklet, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 1037)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings - Payment File, 1975-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1038)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings - Payment File, 1975-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1039)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 1040)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 1041)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1042)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1043)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1044)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1045)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1046)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1047)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 132, Folder 1048)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 132, Folder 1049)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 132, Folder 1050)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 132, Folder 1051)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 132, Folder 1052)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 133, Folder 1053)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 133, Folder 1054)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 133, Folder 1055)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 133, Folder 1056)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Steering Committee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 133, Folder 1057)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Subcommittee Meetings - Payment File, 1976-1979 (Box 133, Folder 1058)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Subcommittee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1059)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Subcommittee Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1060)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Subcommittee Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 134, Folder 1061)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Subcommittee Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 134, Folder 1062)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Regional Meetings - Payment File, 1976 (Box 134, Folder 1063)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Regional Meetings, 1976 (Box 134, Folder 1064)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Comprehensive Arts Planning - Copy of Publication, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 1065)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Comprehensive Arts Planning - Draft (Box 134, Folder 1066)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Comprehensive Arts Planning - Revisions, 1975-1977 (Box 134, Folder 1067)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Comprehensive Arts Planning - Payment File, 1975-1976 (Box 134, Folder 1068)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations, 1977 (Box 135, Folder 1069)
      Copy of Publication
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Responses to Survey (Box 135, Folder 1070)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Responses to Survey (Box 135, Folder 1071)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Responses to Survey (Box 135, Folder 1072)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Summary of Findings (Box 135, Folder 1073)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Correspondence, June 1976-February 1977 (Box 135, Folder 1074)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Correspondence, March-November 1977 (Box 136, Folder 1075)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Correspondence, March-November 1977 (Box 136, Folder 1076)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Correspondence, March-November 1977 (Box 136, Folder 1077)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Information Cards (Box 136, Folder 1078)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Publications - Survey of National Organizations - Information Cards (Box 136, Folder 1079)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Arizona - Alliance for Arts Education, 1974-1978 (Box 137, Folder 1080)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Arizona - Department of Education, 1975-1978 (Box 137, Folder 1081)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Arizona - Department of Education Handbook, 1978 (Box 137, Folder 1082)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California - Alliance for Arts Education - Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 137, Folder 1083)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California - Alliance of California Arts Councils, 1974-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1084)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Brochures, 1971-1973 (Box 137, Folder 1085)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Brochures, 1974-1978 (Box 138, Folder 1086)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 138, Folder 1087)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Statewide Plan, July 1973-April 1975 (Box 138, Folder 1088)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Statewide Plan, July 1973-April 1975 (Box 138, Folder 1089)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Ad Hoc Advisory Commission - Correspondence, September 1974-October 1975 (Box 138, Folder 1090)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Ad Hoc Advisory Commission - Correspondence, September 1974-October 1975 (Box 138, Folder 1091)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Ad Hoc Advisory Commission - Leadership Training, Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 139, Folder 1092)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Ad Hoc Advisory Commission - Leadership Training, Miscellany, 1977-1979 (Box 139, Folder 1093)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 139, Folder 1094)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Department of Education - Miscellany, 1973-1977 (Box 139, Folder 1095)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Arts Commission, 1973-1975 (Box 139, Folder 1096)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - California Arts Legislation, 1974-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1097)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Indiana Alliance for Arts Education, Indiana Arts in Education Center, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 1098)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Indiana Department of Public Instruction Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 139, Folder 1099)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Indiana Department of Public Instruction - Brochures (Box 140, Folder 1100)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Indiana Department of Public Instruction - Development of Statewide Plan, 1971-1976 (Box 140, Folder 1101)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Indiana Department of Public Instruction - Development of Statewide Plan, 1971-1976 (Box 140, Folder 1102)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Indiana Department of Public Instruction - Meetings, 1974-1977 (Box 140, Folder 1103)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Indiana Department of Public Instruction - Miscellany, 1975-1976 (Box 140, Folder 1104)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Massachusetts - Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1971-1974 (Box 141, Folder 1105)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Massachusetts - Department of Education - Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 141, Folder 1106)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Massachusetts - Department of Education - 3rd Annual Arts/Humanities Conference, October 31-November 2, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1107)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Massachusetts - Report of the Governor's Task Force on the Arts and Humanities, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1108)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan Department of Education - Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 141, Folder 1109)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan Department of Education - Development of Statewide Plan, 1975 (Box 141, Folder 1110)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan Department of Education - Development of Statewide Plan, 1976-1977 (Box 142, Folder 1111)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan Department of Education - Brochures (Box 142, Folder 1112)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan - Joint Legislative Committee on the Arts - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 142, Folder 1113)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan - Joint Legislative Committee on the Arts - Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 142, Folder 1114)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan - Joint Legislative Committee on the Arts - Position Paper, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 1115)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Michigan - Joint Legislative Committee on the Arts - Reports, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 1116)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York State Board of Regents, 1970-1979 (Box 143, Folder 1117)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York State Commission on Cultural Resources, 1972-1973 (Box 143, Folder 1118)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Concerned Citizens for the Arts, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 1119)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Council of Educational Associations, 1976 (Box 143, Folder 1120)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Council of Educational Associations - Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 143, Folder 1121)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Council of Educational Associations - Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 143, Folder 1122)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - State Council on the Arts - Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 143, Folder 1123)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - State Council on the Arts - Brochures and Awards, 1969-1975 (Box 143, Folder 1124)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - State Council on the Arts - Brochures General), 1969-1974 (Box 143, Folder 1125)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - State Department of Education - Correspondence, 1967-1979 (Box 144, Folder 1126)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - State Department of Education - Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 144, Folder 1127)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - State Department of Education - Brochures (Box 144, Folder 1128)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Advisory Council on Integrating the Arts into General Education - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 144, Folder 1129)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Advisory Council on Integrating the Arts into General Education - Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 144, Folder 1130)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Advisory Council for Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) Title III - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 1131)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Advisory Council for Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) Title III - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 145, Folder 1132)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Advisory Council for Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) Title III - Meetings, 1971-1978 (Box 145, Folder 1133)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - Advisory Council for Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) Title III - Meetings, 1971-1978 (Box 145, Folder 1134)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - New York - 4-H Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 145, Folder 1135)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Oklahoma - Alliance for Arts Education, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 1136)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Oklahoma - Arts and Humanities Council, 1975-1976 (Box 145, Folder 1137)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Oklahoma - Education Association, 1977 (Box 145, Folder 1138)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Oklahoma - Department of Education - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 145, Folder 1139)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Oklahoma - Department of Education - Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 145, Folder 1140)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Oklahoma - Department of Education - Miscellany, 1975-1977 (Box 146, Folder 1141)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Oklahoma - Summer Arts Institute (Box 146, Folder 1142)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Washington - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 146, Folder 1143)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Washington - Alliance for Arts Education, 1973 (Box 146, Folder 1144)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Washington - Office of Public Instruction - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 146, Folder 1145)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Washington - Office of Public Instruction - Arts Infusion-Research (AIR) for the Handicapped, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 1146)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Washington - Office of Public Instruction - Miscellany (Box 146, Folder 1147)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Washington - State Arts Commission Meeting, October 26-27, 1974 (Box 146, Folder 1148)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Payment File, 1978-1979 (Box 147, Folder 1149)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1150)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Grant #EC7859-E - Proposal, 1977 (Box 147, Folder 1151)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Grant #EC7859-E - Correspondence by City (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1152)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Grant #EC7859-E - Correspondence by City (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1153)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Grant #EC7859-E - Master File by State (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1154)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Grant #EC7859-E - Master File by State (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1155)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Grant #BC7879-E - Master File by State (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1156)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Grant #BC7879-E - Master File by State (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1157)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 148, Folder 1158)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Hartford, 1977-1979 (Box 148, Folder 1159)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Little Rock, 1977-1978 (Box 148, Folder 1160)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Minneapolis, 1977-1978 (Box 148, Folder 1161)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - New York City, 1977-1978 (Box 148, Folder 1162)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Seattle, 1977-1979 (Box 148, Folder 1163)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Winston-Salem, 1977-1978 (Box 148, Folder 1164)
    - Administrative Fellowship Training Program - Arizona, 1977-1979 (Box 148, Folder 1165)